亚历克斯，捂住嘴!
Alex, cover your mouth!
——走吧。-走，走，走，走!
- Let's go. - Move, move, move, move!
武装警察!
Armed police!
武装警察!下来!
Armed police! Get down!
肖恩·华莱士死了。
Sean Wallace is dead.
我重复，肖恩·华莱士…
I repeat, Sean Wallace...
在这里,帮助我。
Here, help me.
明确的。
Clear.
把他弄上车!
Get him in the van!
明确的。
Clear.
他死了吗?
Is he dead?
他的呼吸。开车。
He's breathing. Drive.
快点。
Hurry.
离开了。
Take the left.
除颤器。
Defibrillator.
充电。明确的。冲击。
Charging. Clear. Shock.
好了，我们抓到他了。他的情况很糟糕……
Okay, we have him. He's in a bad way...
缝合到位。现在进入。
Sutures in place. Entering now.
我在哪儿?
Where am I?
我们希望你的合作
We would like your cooperation
关于一个你们称为投资人的团体。
concerning a group you call the Investors.
你会得到回报的。
You would be rewarded.
你为他们工作?
You work for them?
相反。
The opposite.
你们不是警察。
You're not the police.
它的一个版本。
A version of it.
好吧,然后……滚蛋。
Well, then... fuck off.
去你妈的!
Fuck you!
起来!
Get up!
告诉我昨晚的事。鱼市场。
Tell me about last night. The fish market.
一名枪手。男性。三十岁。
One shooter. Male. Thirties.
也许专业?
Maybe professional?
不是很。
Not very.
你看到他的脸了吧?
You saw his face, yes?
没有?
No?
——也许你……-是比利·华莱士
- Perhaps you... - It was Billy Wallace.
肖恩的兄弟。
Sean's brother.
肖恩的兄弟吗?
Sean's brother?
-你能解释一下吗?-我不知道
- Can you explain?  - I don't fucking know.
你让我找到枪手，我找到了。
You asked me to find a shooter, and I did.
你后来去了哪里?嗯?
Where did you go after? Hm?
艾略特帮助杀死比利·华莱士后去了哪里?
Where does Elliot go after he helps kill Billy Wallace?
早餐。
Breakfast.
——早餐。——嗯。
- Breakfast.  - Hm.
你知道,面包。一些花草茶。
You know, toast. Some herbal tea.
毫米毫米毫米。
Mm. Mm. Mm.
我明白了。
I understand.
你就像个秘密特工。
You're like a secret fucking agent.
谁知道你会去哪里……你真正看到的是什么?
Who knows where you go... what you really see?
你看到还有更多的华莱士吗?你告诉我。
You see any more Wallaces out there... you let me know.
嗯?不然我会以为你不喜欢我。
Hm? Or I'll think you don't like me.
比利。
Billy.
把这些。
Take these.
谢谢。
Thanks.
昨晚的枪手是谁?
Who were those shooters last night?
你撞到了什么东西。
You walked into something.
是的,没有大便。我说谢谢了吗?
Yeah, no shit. Have I said thanks?
我不能失去你们两个，比利。
I'm not losing you both, Billy.
-是啊，妈妈告诉我的。-是的…
- Yeah, Mum told me.  - Yeah...
你在跟踪我吗?
Were you following me?
不。走别人的路。你只是运气好。
No. Following someone else. You were just lucky.
鱼市场的那个人，那个杀手，是你吗?
The guy at the fish market, the hit, that was you?
到底怎么回事，肖恩?
What the fuck is going on, Sean?
在车里，你说和你一起来的一个人失踪了。
In the car, you said one of the men you came with went missing.
妈妈的一个手下。
One of Mum's men.
是的。Darragh。
Yeah. Darragh.
他去了銮。我不…
He went to Luan. I don't...
我要和妈妈说话。
I need to speak to Mum.
她有麻烦?
She in trouble?
她会问一些问题。
She'll have some questions.
你的衣服在那里。
Your clothes are there.
达拉和基利安仍然下落不明。菜肴的沉默。
Darragh and Killian are still missing. Luan's gone silent.
-科巴找到人了。——和比利?
- Koba's got to someone.  - And Billy?
-我们说好的，玛丽安。-伦尼在回来的路上了
- We had a deal, Marian. - Lennie's on his way back.
-你说过你能保护我们。——我们离开。
- You said you could protect us. - We're leaving.
或者你可以跑回你的游艇去
Or you can just run off to your yacht
等着他们找到你。
and wait for them to track you down.
记得留点钱。
Just make sure you leave money.
如果我想，我早就这么做了。
If I wanted, I would have done it a long time ago.
芬恩的钱总是引人注目。你知道这一点。
Finn's money will always attract attention. You know this.
我知道战争是什么，玛丽安。我就经历过一次。
I know what war is, Marian. I lived through one.
如果我们现在躲起来，接下来就会狠狠地揍他们。我们不会退缩。
If we hide now, we hit them hard next. We don't back down.
你他妈以为你在跟谁说话?
Who the fuck do you think you're talking to?
我救了你的命，作为交换，我们答应了彼此
I saved your life, and in exchange we promised each other
权力和力量。
power and strength.
你记得你同意了吗?
Do you remember agreeing to that?
她不会拥有我的生活。
She won't have the life I had.
哦，哦，哦，哦，哦。
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
罗兹。罗兹。嘘，嘘，嘘。
Roze. Roze. Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
我们都有自己的计划。
We all have plans for them.
然后他们长大了，一拳打在你脸上。
Then they grow up, punch you in the face.
伦尼回来了。得到你的东西。
Lennie's back. Get your things.
任何东西,从比利?
Anything from Billy?
我会追踪他走的每一步。我会找到他的，我发誓。
I'll track every step he took. I'll find him, I swear.
比利?
Billy?
不,妈妈。是我。
No, Mum. It's me.
这是谁?
Who is this?
这是肖恩,妈妈。
It's Sean, Mum.
这是肖恩。
It's Sean.
我现在无法解释。你得听我说。
I can't explain now. You need to listen to me.
比利是安全的。
Billy's safe.
你得赶紧离开那里。
And you need to get out of there.
科巴来找你了。
Koba's coming for you.
妈妈?妈妈?
Mum? Mum?
妈妈，你在吗?跟我说话，妈妈。
Mum, are you there? Speak to me, Mum.
妈妈，你能听到我说话吗?你在危险!
Mum, can you hear me? You're in danger!
妈妈，你有危险了!
Mum, you're in danger!
我要去找萝丝!
I have to get Roze!
罗兹!
Roze!
罗兹在楼上!我一定要抓住她!
Roze's upstairs! I have to get her!
来吧,快。就是这样。起来，够了!
Come on, quick. That's it. Get up, that's it!
就这样，待在这里。待在这里。呆在那里。保持下来。
That's it, stay here. Stay here. Stay there. Stay down.
——不!——罗兹。
- No!  - Roze.
多环芳烃、多环芳烃、多环芳烃。巴，巴，巴，巴，巴。
Pah, pah, pah. Pah, pah, pah, pah, pah.
罗兹。罗兹。罗兹。
Roze. Roze. Roze.
罗兹!
Roze!
你找到她了吗?
Did you find her yet?
还没有，还在找。
Not yet, still looking.
罗兹,嘘,嘘。
Roze, shh, shh.
来吧。Floriana,起床了。起来，来吧。
Come on. Floriana, get up. Get up, come on.
-我们得离开这里。——哦,罗兹。
- We've got to get out of here. - Oh, Roze.
来吧。来吧。
Come on. Come on.
-把她给我。——在这里。
- Give her to me.  - Here.
伦尼?伦尼?
Lennie? Lennie?
不,不。快跑!我有这个。
No, no. Run! I've got this.
——走吧!走吧!——运行。
- Go! Go!    - Run.
到树林里去，在后面。
To the woods, out back.
去你妈的,玛丽安。去你妈的。
Fuck you, Marian. Fuck you.
他们和你在一起了吗?
Are they with you yet?
还没有。
Not yet.
我寻找。
I'm looking.
找到了给我打电话。
Call me when you have them.
我看到他们。
I see them.
警卫!
Guard!
你想让我在英国法庭上作证
You would like me to testify before a British court...
关于投资人的一切
on everything I know about the Investors.
你会得到国家的全力保护。
You would have the full protection of the state.
你的证据将是匿名的。
Your evidence would be anonymous.
你会变成鬼。
You'd be a ghost.
之后，是新的生活。
Afterwards, a new life.
有一定的限制。
With certain restrictions.
你觉得这会让投资人离开伦敦吗?
And you think that will remove the Investors from London?
根据你脑子里的想法
With what's in your head,
我们会给他们前所未有的打击。
we'll hit them harder than they've ever been hit.
你真他妈蠢。
Well, you're fucking stupid.
如果你想让他们消失，你就得拿走他们控制的东西。
If you want them gone, you have to take what they control.
街的街。黑帮团伙。塔塔。
Street by street. Gang by gang. Tower by tower.
你得把他们彻底摧毁。
You'd have to destroy them from the ground up.
你需要…一个返回的国王。
You need... a returning king.
你炸毁了你父亲的城市。现在你想成为他。
You blew up your father's city. Now you want to be him.
你没有你以为的那么聪明。
You're not as clever as you think you are.
那些想要肖恩·华莱士死的人
The people who wanted Sean Wallace dead...
你才刚刚碰到他们。
you've only just brushed up against them.
我研究这个已经很多年了。
I've been on this for years.
城市的改变。投资方有了新玩家。
The city's changed. The Investors have a new player.
他们不会看到我来的。就像你说的，我是个鬼。
They won't see me coming. Like you said, I'm a ghost.
我需要我的世界里的人。一个帮派。
I'll need people from my world. A gang.
她在哪里呢?
Where is she?
不可能的。
Impossible.
她对我很有价值。一个交易资产。
She's of high value to me. A trading asset.
卖给她的敌人?
To sell to her enemies?
政治。
Politics.
你不是这里的全部。
You're not the whole picture here.
然后没有达成任何协议。
Then no deal.
你信任她吗?
You trust her?
我说了我需要她。
I said I need her.
她的军事训练。
Her military training.
她的人。
Her people.
来了。
Come.
跟我来。
Follow me.
那宅。那宅……
Go with Naza. Naza...
我没有清晰的记忆。
I don't have clear memories.
我记得拉尔，她的人民，
I remember Lale, her people,
他们把我从酒店里拉了出来。
they pulled me out of that hotel.
然后呢?
Then what?
他们找到了能把我复原的人。
They found someone to put me back together.
这些都是拉尔的人干的?
Lale's people did all that?
是的。
Yeah.
为什么?
Why?
我帮助了他们，不是吗?
I helped them, didn't I?
他们偿还债务。
They repay their debts.
听我的。科巴已经掐住他们的脖子了。
Listen to me. Koba's got them by the neck now.
他从他们的利润中抽了很大一部分，
He takes a hefty cut of their profits,
当他们包装他的产品时，他像鹰一样盯着。
and whilst they package his product, he watches like a hawk.
我得尽快带你去更安全的地方，妈妈。
I need to get you somewhere safer soon, Mum.
你在这里多久了?
How long have you been here?
3个月。
3 months.
它必须是这样。
It had to be this way.
你只要拿起电话就行了
All you had to do was pick up the phone
告诉我们你还活着。
and tell us you were still breathing.
-那是有风险的-我都不知道你还活着。
- It would have been a risk. - I didn't even know you were alive.
没有他那操蛋的家人，我过得更轻松。他说得有道理。
It was easier without his fuck-up family. He's got a point.
你到底在做什么?
What have you been doing exactly?
塔。这笔钱。团伙。
The towers. The money. The gangs.
-我要收回我说的话-他们把你的头治好了吗?
- I'm taking it all back. - Did they fix your head right?
-我是说真的。-和一群恐怖分子?
- I mean it.  - With a bunch of terrorists?
——认真?-其他人也会加入。
- Seriously?  - Others will join.
一旦他们意识到科巴不是未来，我就是。
Once they realise Koba's not the future, I am.
但你得退一步。科巴侵入了你们的网络。
But you need to step back. Koba's got inside your networks.
你不知道该相信谁。
You don't know who to trust.
如果我要收留我父亲的女朋友，
And if I'm to give shelter to my father's girlfriend,
我要知道你欠她什么。
I need to know what you owe her.
她救了我的命。
She saved my life.
然后她的家人。
Then she's family.
在这里。用这个代替。
Here. Use this instead.
嘘,嘘。
Shh, shh.
他想当国王，不是吗?
He wants to be king, doesn't he?
他的叛军在这里。
He's got his little rebel army here.
那你该怎么办?
Where does that leave you?
试着睡一会儿吧。
Try and get some sleep.
别假装什么都没发生。
Don't pretend this isn't happening.
他会来找你要所有的钱
He'll come to you, ask for all the money,
这就是结束的时候。
and that's when it's over.
-不可能的——没有。因为我不会答应的。
- That's not gonna happen. - No. Because I won't say yes.
嘘，嘘，嘘。
Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
我是肖恩。
I'm Sean.
-这里一切都好吗?-我知道更糟的。
- Is everything all right here? - I've known worse.
我敢打赌。
I bet.
我可以吗?
May I?
你好。
Hello.
我还以为爸爸会回头看我呢。
I was expecting to see Dad looking back at me.
但是没有。不是华莱士的眼睛。
But no. Not the Wallace eyes.
幸运的突破。
Lucky break.
罗兹。嘘,嘘,嘘。
Roze. Shh, shh, shh.
这是怎么呢
What's going on?
科巴的人带走了罗詹。
Koba's men took Rojan.
他们想要什么?
What do they want?
罗扬在做副业。科巴一定发现了。
Rojan was selling on the side. Koba must have found out.
我们还有什么选择?科巴拿走了我们大部分的利润。
What choice do we have? Koba takes most of our profits.
这些钱不够寄回家。
There's not enough to send home.
我们说好要小心的。
We agreed to be careful.
谨慎?
Careful?
如果科巴在这里找到了玛丽安·华莱士呢?
What if Koba found Marian Wallace here?
我们和肖恩·华莱士有协议
Our deal was with Sean Wallace.
-不是他的家人。-我来处理。
- Not his family.  - I'll handle it.
自从你回来人们就一直在议论。
People have been talking since you came back.
她还知道自己是谁吗?
Does she still know who she is?
你妈妈在这里，这对我们来说是个问题。
This is a problem for us, your mother being here.
我们会为我的家人找个地方。
We'll find somewhere for my family.
我的人不能再这样下去了。
My people can't continue like this.
时机成熟时我们就去袭击科巴。
We'll hit Koba when the time's right.
耐心不是问题所在。
Patience is not the problem.
他们需要相信你能兑现你的承诺。
They need faith that you can deliver what you promised.
你在压力下。我明白了。
You're under pressure. I understand.
他们需要对你有信心。
They need faith in you.
你为什么回来找我?
Why did you come back for me?
你知道的太多了。我是在保护自己。
You know too much. I was protecting myself.
很高兴知道这一点。
That's good to know.
如果你想要你声称的，你必须做好准备
If you want what you claim, you must be prepared
做任何事都无所畏惧，无所顾虑。
to do everything without fear, without care.
这是它对你的要求。
This is what it asks of you.
格鲁吉亚人来了。
The Georgians are coming.
他们有Rojan。
They've got Rojan.
哦,狗屎。
Oh, shit.
你得躲起来。来吧。科巴的人来了。
You need to hide. Come on. Koba's men are here.
- - - - - -快。-发生什么事了?
- Quick.   - What's going on?
- - - - - -快。加油！加油——妈妈,走了。
- Quick. Come on, come on. - Mum, go.
走，走，走，走，走。
Go, go, go, go, go.
快。
Quick.
Merwan……
Merwan...
——生活怎么样?——好。
- How's life?   - Good.
幸福的妻子，幸福的生活，是吗?
Happy wife, happy life, eh?
-我有个问题。毫米。
- I have a question.   - Mm.
您对产品的质量满意吗?
Are you happy with the quality of the product?
顾客满意吗?——是的。
- Are the customers happy?   - Yes.
你的员工需要工作的时间，
The hours your employees are required to work,
我们谈过了，对吧?
we negotiated that, yes?
我们要求每天工作10小时。这是可以接受的吗?
We asked for 10 hours a day. That is acceptable?
待在这里。
Stay here.
每小时的工资，有问题吗?没有?
The hourly rate, is that a problem? No?
不。
No.
所以我们之间没有什么大问题，对吧?
So there's no general big problem between us, correct?
——没有。——没有。
- No.   - No.
哦,我的爱。不,不!
Oh, my love. No, no!
所以…这个小偷……
So... this thief...
他只是个小问题，仅此而已。
he's a small problem, nothing more.
为什么?
Why?
你从来没有让他去偷东西因为你并不不快乐，对吧?
You never asked him to steal because you are not unhappy, huh?
他是你哥哥，对吗?我是说，亲兄弟?
He's your brother, yes? I mean, real brother?
同样的母亲吗?
The same mother?
你们都称呼对方为兄弟姐妹。
You all call each other brother, sister.
-我只是看看。-他是我哥哥。
- I'm just checking.   - He's my brother.
-嘿…——没有。
- Hey...   - No.
我觉得你哥哥在骗我。
I think your brother is lying to me.
不。
No.
哦!你想取代他的位置。
Oh! You want to take his place.
不。不,不……
No. No, no...
好吧!
Okay!
给你的手。
Give your hand.
不。不,不。
No. No, no.
不,一。不。
No, Tamaz. No.
不!
No!
嘘，嘘，嘘。
Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
请告诉你的工人，现在轮班12小时。
Please tell your workers, the shift is now 12 hours.
嗯。
Eh.
我们递送的更多，你们包装的更多。
We deliver more, you package more.
赢了,赢了。
Win, win.
我们走吧。
Let's go.
库尔德人那边进展如何?
How's it progressing with the Kurds?
科巴对我们来说是个更大的问题。
Koba's becoming a bigger problem for us.
我已经控制住了。
I've got it under control.
你父亲的女朋友和你母亲一起工作?
And your father's girlfriend working with your mother?
我说了我在处理。
I said I'm handling it.
报复的机会已经不多了，肖恩。
The window to retaliate is closing, Sean.
对不起。
Sorry.
你想让我……吗?
Do you want me to...?
嘘。
Shh.
你想让她和我们一样吗?
Do you want her to be like us?
你觉得我不该来这里吗?
You think I shouldn't be here?
你可以做你喜欢做的事。
You can do what you like.
我父亲是个赌徒。他为黑手党做赌注。
My father was a gambler. He ran bets for the mafia.
他不想，但你不能拒绝。
He didn't want to, but you don't say no.
然后他拒绝了。
Then he said no.
他们在我们厨房朝他脑袋开了一枪。
They shot him in the head in our kitchen.
我弟弟也是。
My little brother too.
这样他就不会长大后去复仇了。
So he wouldn't grow up and take vengeance.
我知道这是什么世界。
I know what this world is.
罗兹。
Roze.
你有多了解我母亲?
How well do you know my mother?
也许我知道一些你不知道的事。
Maybe I know some things you don't.
那你就知道她最后会毁了你。
Then you'll know that she'll screw you over in the end.
拉尔，长老们开会了。
Lale, the elders have called a meeting.
我们得谈谈华莱士一家。
We need to discuss the Wallaces.
肖恩。
Sean.
在你之后。
After you.
我听说你不开心。我怎样才能让你快乐?
I'm told you're unhappy. How can I make you happy?
你母亲的行为，栾安，对我们没有帮助。
The actions of your mother, Luan, this does not help us.
科巴闻到了叛乱的味道，所以他逼我们。
Koba smells rebellion, so he pushes us.
利润太少，不能寄回家。
There is too little profit to send home.
我们和这个城市的其他人不一样，对吧?
We're not the same as others in this city, yeah?
那些为了权力而追求权力的人。
Those who want power for its own sake.
我的人民希望在我们的家园获得自由。
My people want freedom in our homelands.
如果我们的生意像现在这样失败了，
If our business here fails, as it fails now,
对我们来说，还有其他城市，
for us there are other cities,
其他继续斗争的方式。
other ways to continue the struggle.
你的生意不会失败。
Your business won't fail.
等科巴走了，你就能在这城市有立足之地了。
When Koba's gone, you'll have a place in this city.
我答应过你的。
I promised you that.
太慢了。
Too slow.
我说过谁支持科巴，我就打谁。
I said I'd hit anyone who sides with Koba.
现在这还不够。是时候升级了。
That's not enough now. It's time to escalate.
我们愿意分享你的信心。
We'd like to share your confidence.
是的，我们需要彼此。
Yeah, we need each other.
但你更需要我们。没有我们，你是孤独的。
But you need us more. Without us, you're alone.
我会给你钱寄回家。
I'll give you money to send home.
我会给你未来战斗的武器。
I'll give you weapons for the fight ahead.
这些东西是你给的吗?
These things are yours to give?
你妈妈有她自己的野心，不是吗?
Your mother has her own ambitions, no?
我说过了，我向你保证。
Like I said, you have my word.
让我们看看。
Then let us see.
我记得这个。
I remember this.
街头杂音，不是吗?
Street grunt, isn't it?
举起手来。
Hands up.
前面的座位。来吧。
Front seat. Come on.
我以为我在你的追杀名单上会更靠前。
Thought I'd be higher up your kill list.
有趣。有人告诉我你是禁区。
Funny. I was told you were off limits.
约瑟夫的歌手。他非常坚持。
Joseph Singer. He was very insistent.
原来你和我是一伙的。现在。
Turns out you and I are on the same side. For now.
我才不在乎你和辛格。
I do not give a fuck about you or Singer.
但Koba。尤其是你一直在杀他的新朋友。
But Koba would. Especially as you've been killing his new friends.
看到这个吗?
See this here?
外科医生说不管怎样一根头发，噗……
The surgeon said a hair either way and, pff...
奇迹,真的。
Miracle, really.
然后我想，他是故意的吗?
Then I thought, did he mean to do it?
这是艾略特。只要问心无愧，什么都可以。
That's very Elliot. Anything for a clean conscience.
说声谢谢。
Say thank you.
你真会撒谎。
You're such a good liar.
你连自己的屁话都信了。
You even fall for your own bullshit.
我说的是最坏的情况。芬恩的文件很大。
I asked for the worst case, you know. Finn's file was huge.
洗钱，勒索，阴谋
Money laundering, extortion, conspiracy,
暴杀，暴杀，谋杀，绑架，贩卖。
ABH, GBH, murder, kidnap, trafficking.
你的……是空的。
Yours... was empty.
没什么。没有人在乎。
Nothing. No one cares.
你是一个无关紧要的。
You're an irrelevance.
你不是你爸爸
You're not your dad
这些你都不知道该怎么做。
and you don't know how to do any of this.
你做完了吗?
You finished?
辛格说你回来了，但你想退出。
Singer said you're back in, but you want out.
下定决心吧。我们都知道你来这里的真正目的。
Make your mind up. We both know why you're really here.
你和我的目标一致。
You and I want the same thing.
把投资人赶出这座城市。
To rid this city of the Investors.
所以要么帮我，要么滚蛋。
So either help me or fuck off.
那么,继续。
Go on, then.
你是对的。
You're right.
不需要。你们都躲在一个屋檐下。
Don't have to. You're all hiding under one roof.
只要把科巴·拉尔的地址给我，
Could just give Koba Lale's address,
这是所有华莱士的集合，对吧?
and that's all the Wallaces in one, right?
我们不是一条船上的。
We're not on the same side.
肖恩在哪儿?
Where's Sean?
他说你和你的人救了他的命。
He says you and your people saved his life.
这对你有什么好处，拉尔?
What's in this for you, Lale, hm?
看到我回来，你一定很伤心。
Must have killed you to see me walking back in here.
你以为你把他玩弄于股掌之间了，是吗?
Thought you had him wrapped around your little finger, didn't you?
这对你来说很难，是吧?
This is hard for you, isn't it?
是什么?
What is?
他不再害怕你了。
He's not scared of you anymore.
他在屋顶等你。
He's waiting for you on the roof.
肖恩，怎么了?
Sean, what's going on?
你他妈去哪了?
Where the fuck have you been?
关于发生在我身上的事我撒了谎。
I lied about what happened to me.
-我要你听仔细了。——没有。
- I want you to listen closely.  - No.
你听我说。我受够了。
You listen to me. I've had enough.
你再撒一个谎，我们就结束了。
One more lie out of your mouth and we're done.
我中枪后，没和拉尔的人在一起。
After I was shot, I wasn't with Lale's people.
我被别人带走了。
I was taken by someone else.
我是一个俘虏。拉尔。
I was a captive. Lale too.
投资人还有其他敌人。
The Investors have other enemies.
他们中的一些人在我们的政府内部。
Some of them inside our government.
它们行踪诡秘，数量稀少
They're secretive and they're few,
他们想让投资人离开
and they want the Investors out.
他们和我想要的是一样的。
They and I want the same thing.
你想要什么?
What are you after?
我想让你知道一切。我希望我们之间能重新开始。
I want you to know everything. I want a clean slate between us.
不。
No.
你想要什么?
What do you want?
我要你把爸爸的钱给我。
I want you to give me Dad's money.
我要你的手臂接触器。
And I want your arms contacts.
你能做到吗?
Can you do that?
你和弗罗里安娜是怎么相处的?
You and Floriana, how does it work?
算了吧。
Forget it.
她控制着账户。这是你父亲安排的。
She controls the accounts. Your father saw to that.
那么它是如何工作的呢?你请吗?
So how does it work, then? Do you beg?
当我身边没有别人的时候，她帮助了我。
She helped me when there was nobody else around for me.
-我不能夺走她的一切-你老了变得多愁善感。
- I can't just take everything from her. - Grown sentimental in your old age.
——滚蛋。-我才是你不信任的人!
- Fuck off.  - I'm the one you don't trust!
-没错，我不相信你，肖恩——我很抱歉。
- Bloody right I don't trust you, Sean. - I'm sorry.
不,你不是。你只会后悔你要乞求我的东西。
No, you're not. You're only sorry you're having to beg for what's mine.
-我应该告诉你我还活着。-是的，你应该这么做!
- I should have told you I was alive. - Yes, you should have!
-我以为你死了。——我很抱歉。
- I thought you were dead.  - I'm sorry.
——我很抱歉。-你把我钉死在十字架上!
- I'm sorry.  - You crucified me!
我很抱歉。我很抱歉。
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
对不起。
Sorry.
日复一日，周复一周，月复一月，
There were days and weeks and months,
当我忘记我是谁的时候，我的脑子里剩下的部分。
inside what was left of my head, when I forgot who I was.
但我现在知道了。
But I know now.
我是华莱士。
I'm a Wallace.
我他妈是华莱士家的人，要么全有，要么全无。
I'm a fucking Wallace, all or nothing.
我会保护我们，得到我们应得的。
And I'm gonna protect us and get what we deserve.
要有耐心。你很快就会收到钱的，好吗?
Be patient. You'll receive the money soon, okay?
什么时候?什么时候?我不知道是什么时候。
When? When? I don't know when.
你的人民需要帮助。
Your people need help.
如果你指望肖恩·华莱士，那就大错特错了。
If you're looking to Sean Wallace, it would be a mistake.
我可以给你更好的。
I can offer you something better.
我有办法。
I have the means.
和连接。
And the connections.
我继续吗?
Shall I continue?
这是一个条件。
There would be a condition.
什么?
What?
我能告诉你一个秘密吗?
Can I tell you a secret?
爸爸很怕你。
Dad was scared of you.
他知道你比他聪明。
He knew you were smarter than him.
你是故意迷路的，对吧?
You got lost on purpose, didn't you?
所以他不想让你卷进来。
So he'd never want you involved.
你能看清人的本质。
You see people for what they are.
你从不放过任何机会，对吧?
You don't miss a trick, do you?
我需要你在这里，保护我。
I need you here, watching my back.
比利，你会那样做吗?
Will you do that, Billy?
是的,我会的。
Yeah, I will.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
跟我来。
Come with me.
我跟拉尔和默万谈过了。
I've spoken with Lale and Merwan.
从现在开始，我会支持他们的生意。
From now on, I will support their business.
这是真的吗?
Is this true?
你可真是个大忙人。
Well, you're a busy devil.
你也会这么对我的。
You would have done this to me.
那你现在想让我做什么?
So what would you like me to do now?
离开。
Leave.
你本可以得到你想要的。
You could have had what you wanted.
但你却不敢这么做。
But you're afraid to do it.
你会得到我答应你的。
You'll have what I promised.
(#“我们走错了”，奶油)
(# "We're Going Wrong", Cream)
#请#
# Please #
睁开你的眼睛
# Open your eyes #
# #试
# Try #
#意识到……＃
# To realise... #
我今天才知道
# I found out today #
我们走错路了
# We're going wrong #
#请#
# Please #
睁开你的眼睛
# Open your eyes #
我今天才知道
# I found out today #
我们走错路了
# We're going wrong #